(Leonard:)...the dark matter signal found
in sodium-iodide crystals by the Italians.
(Beverley:)So no original research?
(Howard:)No.
BEVERLY:
What's the point of my seeing it?
(Beverley:)I could just read the paper
the Italians wrote.
Okay, just for the record, we're not
in an ersatz homosexual relationship.
(Raj:)Well, then,
why didn't you say that to her?
- Why is it always my responsibility?
- Oh, it's not always your responsibility.
(Raj:)I swear, this is the same thing you did
at the comic book store last week.
(Howard:)I can't believe you're bringing that up.
- I didn't bring it up. You did.
- We'll talk about this later.
Well, you always say that,
but we never do.
(Sheldon:)You went to the comic book store
without me?
- Hey.
- You got alcohol?